Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-van-khoa-225337192 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Go (Programming Language)
NextJS

Tailwind CSS

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Nguyen Van Khoa

Software Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I'm currently working as a Software Engineer. I have more than 2 years of working experience in developing and maintaining software with C++. I'm familiar with Linux and Window OS.

Programming language: C++

Good to know: Typescript (NextJS), Go

Please reach out to me at:

- Email: anthony2742000@gmail.com

- Phone: 0962898579

Experience

Endava

Software Developer

February 2023 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Main project: Core Middleware (CoreMW) - Opensaf

Team CBA - FBI (8 people)

Main language: C++, Java, Bash Script

- Contributed to develop & maintain components of CoreMW project using C+

+.

- Contributed to create testsuites for testing and development by using Python and Java on Jenkin (Sles 12&15)
- Communicated with International customers to get their requirements and provide solutions to them for developing.

Bosch Vietnam

Software Engineer Internship

April 2022 - October 2022 (7 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Working on Linux OS.
- Study about framework Qt/ Qml (learning level).
- Examined 2-wheel Project System (launching systems with Raspberry Pi4 to push data from Sygic-map to motorcycle screen (Cable, Bluetooth) by using LVGL and typescript of Raspberry Pi OS).

Page 1 of 2

- Read source codes and logs of data for debugging and maintaining for 2-wheel System by C++.
- Wrote requirements and documents for launching system and review logs, including changes to maintain system. (changes from the application version to match the system).

FPT Software

Software Engineer September 2020 - March 2021 (7 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Examined Embedded System (read source codes and implemented functions based on Sequence Diagram using C++).
- Wrote unit tests by using stdout for debugging and wrote reports for customers.
- Fixed code smell and improved tech wealth.
- Contributed to FPT public SVN and Gitlab for C++.

Education

Bach Khoa University (fomerly Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology)

Engineer's degree, Computer Science · (September 2018 - June 2023)